<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-12-26T12:31:32+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Anton’s Blog</title><subtitle>A peek inside my thoughts.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/26/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2017-12-26T11:36:59+02:00</published><updated>2017-12-26T11:36:59+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/26/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/12/26/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Use it or lose it</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/comfort/zone/fear/nature/skills/knowledge/2017/12/26/use-it-or-lose-it.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Use it or lose it" /><published>2017-12-26T11:36:59+02:00</published><updated>2017-12-26T11:36:59+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/comfort/zone/fear/nature/skills/knowledge/2017/12/26/use-it-or-lose-it</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/comfort/zone/fear/nature/skills/knowledge/2017/12/26/use-it-or-lose-it.html">&lt;p&gt;I want to undestand how our mind works and what are the reasons for our feelings.
Woudn’t it be nice if we could control our feelings?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I noticed that I intentionally defer doing one specific task. But why?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This task involves using a tool I started learning how to use before 10 months.
But&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9 months ago I started learning Elixir.
I had great fun with it, but I stopped using it 5 months ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to use the language soon again, but&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a big queue of tasks waiting for me to complete them.
But what is their order? Which task do I do next?
Usually the tasks with the nearest deadline have the highest priority.
But there are ta&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;why do i fear of something?
for example i have been writing in the programming language Elixir
i had a great experience before 7 months
but since the i haven’t touched the language
a lot of time has passed
now i have to do a project in that language
and i am scared, i fear the project, the language… why?
it is because a lot of time has passed
and i am not as confident in my knowledge as before
it means that it has escaped my comfort zone
it’s use it or you lose it
i would have to struggle again to expand my comfort zone&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;we can imagine the universe of all skills and knowledge like nature
it grows wild as time passes, if humans don’t interact with nature
for example i have the skill of programming in Elixir
when i have started learning it, i went into the wild
i had to expand my comfort zone
because i am not comfortable in the wild with all these poisonous plants and dangerous animals
i had to carefully build my comfort zone there under the form of a house/building
the bigger and the more secure the building, the bigger and more secure the comfort zone
for Elixir i managed to build a wooden 1-floored cabin without windows
and thus after 4 months plants weaved around it and animals started living in the small house
this is because the owner of the house didn’t maintain it
the master of this zone didn’t use it, so he lost it
he would have to build it again&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;but on the bright side, he already has experience building this house
he/she can now build it even better, even faster :)&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I want to undestand how our mind works and what are the reasons for our feelings. Woudn’t it be nice if we could control our feelings?</summary></entry></feed>